gunsnfreedom.com 2019-05-25

# Affiliate Disclosure & Privacy

## **Privacy Policy for Gunsnfreedom.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us through our [contact page](http://gunsnfreedom.com/contact/ "Contact").

At Gunsnfreedom.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Gunsnfreedom.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, Gunsnfreedom.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Gunsnfreedom.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Gunsnfreedom.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Gunsnfreedom.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Clickbank  
Chitika  
Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Gunsnfreedom.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Gunsnfreedom.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Gunsnfreedom.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

## Affiliate Disclosure Statement

This affiliate disclosure is a part of, and is subject to, the terms and conditions policy of this website. The terms and conditions policy for this website may be viewed [here](http://articleviper.com/terms "Terms & Conditions").

The GunsnFreedom.com website and blog uses affiliate programs and sponsorships as a means of supplemental monetization. If you choose to click on links to products and services mentioned by either the owner(s) or guest writers of this website and make a purchase, a commission will be paid to either the website owner(s) or the guest writer.

This website and blog does contain content which might present a conflict of interest or be considered to have an influence on the opinions given. This content may not always be identified.

A few of the affiliate programs used by this website and blog include, but are not limited to, Amazon.com, Warrior Forum, Clickbank, and more.

Products recommended by this website, exclusive of those recommended by Guest writers, are chosen based on having been used or thoroughly researched by the owner(s) of this website. They are chosen with the intent of providing readers with tools that will help to enhance their online efforts. Because our reputation and credibility is highly valued by us, we will make every effort to only recommend products we feel will add value to our visitor’s marketing efforts. Products that do not meet our expectations will either be given mixed reviews or those reviews will not be included.

### Third Party & Sponsor Ads

At times, text and image ads may be added to the content and sidebar of this website. These text and image ads are provided by a third party such as Google AdSense or sponsor ads.

Products and services recommended by Guest writers are also included under the heading of third party recommendations. This website does not personally endorse the products and services advertised in these third party ads unless otherwise stated. Sponsor companies are not affiliated with GunsnFreedom.com, however, Guest writers may be affiliated in some manner.

### Due Diligence

As a visitor to this website, you agree that you are solely responsible for performing your own due diligence before making a purchase of any product or service recommended by this website, Guest writers, or sponsored, third party ads. You agree that you assume responsibility for any outcomes from purchases made of said products or services. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

### Reporting

While we attempt to always provide recommendations for products and services that have good reputations, occasionally a product may not deliver the same experience to other parties. If you have had a less than happy experience with a product that we recommend, please let us know by using our [contact page](http://gunsnfreedom.com/contact/ "Contact"). We will look into the situation and determine if our support of that product or service is to continue.

### Updates

This affiliate disclosure is subject to change without notice. Please check back frequently to review its content.

This Affiliate Disclosure was last updated on: July 31, 2013

NASA is warning that we have 13 months to get ready.  See why FEMA has ordered 300 million body bags in the face of what some are calling WWIII. **[CLICK HERE](http://52b9e9wzui7kltqj6dyfxcuisv.hop.clickbank.net/?tid=SURVBOTPOST "Survive End Days")** (sponsored)
